Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Here you go. You earned this fair and square, Asta.
What, you don't want it?
No! I do, I do, I do!
This is really mine!
Well, what are you waiting for? Let's see how it looks.
And now, the finishing touch.
Hey! Looks pretty good on you. Right, Yami?
I don't think it's his color.
It's official now. You're one of us. You're a member of the Black Bulls.
Don't do anything that would bring shame to Yami, or to the Black Bulls.
Understood! I'm so glad to be a part of this team!
Shut up, kids.
I'm so sorry! I'll be more careful from now on, sir!
What? Lord, shut up! Do you not understand?
So I guess that's the other new recruit.
Little insect.
Me
Wily na ka no naja na ni ni hitoz kanläwamai
わかってる わかってるんだ
獣王無人にどこまでも 羽ばかけたらな
いつの日も夢見てた
それでもいっぱいもしかしかな
世界でも何度もか彫り立てる
本能のまま諦めしたいからさ
遥か未来へ 今駆け出したんだ
まだ見ぬ不安さは全て越えて
あの日描いた僕が僕であるために
いつの日でページの続けがあるよ
君のよう希望と
まるでいつかのワンページのような
君と僕ら出会えた
これを奇跡って呼ぼうか
聴覧も出来る
angen部屋だ
すくないね
みたいさ
そのうちによくなり
フレヲの一番
昼を巡っておきます
あなたと statutoryした
あなたはそれがレベル!!
Develop cerain
おいしいわ
お笑いはすぎみ
大ate状況 hélasか
This is the first time I've ever had a space of my own!
Back at the church, everybody crammed into one room!
We were all lined up like sardines!
So long, dust! Dirt and grime, get out of here!
See ya, cobwebs!
Go on, scrub all you want.
We're free till the next mission, anyway.
Oh, hey, one more thing, Asta.
Yeah, what's up?
Make sure you take some time to write.
The folks back at the church deserve a letter.
They're your family, right?
So, they'll want to know that you're okay.
Right!
You can't go making anyone worry.
That's what being a real man is all about.
Later.
Just hit me up if you need anything.
Will do! Thanks, Magna!
This is my first castle, but not my last.
Someday, I'm gonna live in the castle of the Wizard King.
I won't lose. Got that, Yuno?
It's better than you deserve.
A room like this is wasted on the likes of you.
Now, tomorrow I'll explain your duties as a magic knight.
I don't particularly wish to be your tutor.
But since it's on Captain Vajjan's orders, so be it.
Are you listening, boy?
My name is Yuno.
My name is Yuno, Klaus. Not boy.
Enough. Watch your tone.
I outrank you. You are to address me as sir.
Yes, sir.
Better.
Don't be late tomorrow. I will be displeased.
I will be displeased.
...
Thank you.
I knew we were right about you, Yuno!
The pride and joy of Hajj, making it into the Magic Knights.
Not that I'm surprised.
Yuno can do anything!
Yeah, anything!
Everyone in the village will be so excited when they hear.
And what does Asta's letter say?
Can you even make out that terrible chicken scratch of his?
Yeah, he writes like a five-year-old.
So does he say when he's coming home?
When he does give here, we'll have to cheer him up.
Even Asta will have a hard time bouncing back from this.
Maybe a pot-potato party will lift his spirits.
Actually, he says that he got in.
They both passed.
What?!
Seriously?!
Mm-hmm.
Oh, wow.
You're not kidding, are you?
Really?
He did it!
So, um, I guess that Asta won't be coming home, will he?
Right!
We'll go let everyone know about our Magic Knights!
This will be the best news Hajj Village has ever gotten to!
Amazing!
He's gonna be a Magic Knight just like he said!
He did it!
Asta, you know?
Good job!
Just keep doing your best!
So it's real, I wasn't dreaming!
Right!
Yeah!
I'm ready to go-
Wait a second!
I'm pretty sure this column wasn't here yesterday!
Hey, newbie!
How's it hanging?
Oh, uh, I'm good, thanks.
Can I ask you, though, about this column?
Yeah, what about it?
Well, it's just, I don't think it was here yesterday.
Probably because it wasn't.
That's nothing, though.
This whole building shifts around all the time.
It does?!
Yeah!
Hey, I'll get used to it.
I thought there was something weird about this place.
Well, come on!
Let's go!
Sure thing!
You're lucky enough to have me as your tour guide.
There's no one better to show you all the secrets of the Black Bull's hideout.
Well, Rasta, ready?
Yeah, I'm ready!
Let's go, Mr. Shades!
What?
No!
It's Sir Twerp!
Right!
Got it, Sir Twerp!
Drop the Twerp!
This is the dining hall!
Ooh!
Yeah, what'd you think?
Ridiculously huge, huh?
No kidding!
It's enormous!
And this is the communal bath.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's so hot!
I mean, maybe it is for a normal person, but this heat should be nothing to a black ball.
What's wrong?
Do you want to get out already?
No, of course not!
I can stay in!
I'm not done yet!
Over there's where the women's rooms are!
If a guy goes in, the trap magic will kill him!
Wow, serious security!
And here is...
Huh?
The bathroom!
Ah!
You're dead.
We're really sorry, sir!
Whoa!
What's in there?
That's the Beast Room.
Uh, what for?
It's Yami's little hobby.
And Austin?
Yeah?
What's up?
I've decided to put you in charge of our furry friends.
What?
This job is an honor to have, you know?
I hate to give it up, but it's yours.
They get fed in the morning and in the evening.
Go on, give it a shot.
Okay, nice little beasties.
Here you go.
Eat up!
Ah!
The Black Bull's library!
Got it!
And this beauty here's the rec room.
You can have lots of fun in here.
Uh-huh!
Say what now?
Ah!
What's the matter, newbie?
Can't keep up?
Just wait!
You haven't seen anything yet!
Ha!
I'll show you!
Ah!
Ow!
Geez, give a guy some warning.
What the?
Who is she?
A Black Bull's robe.
So that means...
Well, what do you know?
It's your fellow rookie.
She's our other new member this year.
Cool!
Another newbie?
Glad to know I'm not alone!
How's it going?
I'm Asta from Hodge Village!
Let's give this all we've got!
What do you say?
Don't speak to me so casually!
You're a little insect of a commoner, with barely any mana.
Little insect!
Gee, commoner?
My name is Noelle Silva, of the Royal Silva House.
What?
No way!
Are you...
Royalty!
I, uh...
An insignificant insect like me should never have presumed to speak so informally to
an exalted royal such as yourself!
As long as you understand.
Wait.
Who are you calling a little insect?
We joined the Magic Knights at the same time, didn't we?
Who cares if you're royalty?
Yeah, that's right, Asuka!
You kill her!
Being royal doesn't matter here!
It does very much so.
And what makes you so sure?
Ah...
Foolish commoners.
I suppose words aren't enough to make you understand.
The difference in our magic power should get the point across.
Hey!
Wait a minute!
Don't forget your place again!
There's no time!
What were you thinking?
Entitled brat.
Obviously you've got more guts than sense.
You just attacked a senior member!
It isn't my fault you were in the wrong place.
I didn't tell you to stand there.
You did that on your own.
What kind of crazy are you?
I'm your superior here!
That's nice, but I'm royalty.
Yeah?
Well, I don't care if you're royalty or the sister of the Silver Eagle's captain!
Yami's the only person I know who would ever take on a crazy chick like you!
So you might want to show some gratitude.
I was holding off because you're a woman, but I think it's time for your baptism!
Don't bother!
I quit this stupid squad!
You...
Hey!
What do you think you're doing, huh?
I'm leaving before the filth of the Black Bulls has a chance to rub off on me!
Everyone knows you're the worst of the worst Magic Knight squads.
This is hardly the place for a royal like me!
How dare you!
Get back here and apologize to the robe and Yami!
Apologize!
I gave everything to get that robe and she just threw it away!
You moron!
I don't get it.
What the hell just happened?
How did I wind up outside?
I was just looking for the bathroom.
Huh?
Ah!
Jeez, what the heck was that thing?
What's she doing?
Ah!
Oh!
It is...
Why won't it work?
Why can't I ever hit?
What I'm aiming for!
So it's true.
Everything they said about me.
Have you heard?
Apparently the youngest Silva child has no control over her magic power.
Oh no!
For someone like that to be born into the royal family?
That sad grimoire of yours is practically paper thin!
Are you sure you're really royalty?
Not being able to control your own magic.
That's the most pitiful thing I've ever heard.
And this wretch is my little sister?
Embarrassing.
You will never be a member of my squad.
There is no room in the Silver Eagles for a disgrace like you.
A disgrace and a mistake.
Why wasn't it you who died instead of our mother?
What an abject failure.
I am not a failure!
Somehow, I will make you accept me!
Poor Noelle.
I guess she doesn't have it easy either.
Hey!
The little insect!
How long have you been there?
Here it comes.
The mocking!
Are you...
You will never be a member of my squad.
There is no room in the Silver Eagles for a disgrace.
Not being able to control your own magic.
That's the most pitiful thing I've ever heard.
Are you sure you're really royalty?
No!
No?
Take this!
Dump taken.
Guess it's time for a catnap.
Huh?
What in the hell was that?
My goodness.
Cool!
That's magic power gone out of control.
And a whole hell of a lot of it, too.
We're gonna have to do something.
Well, attacking the thing with magic is out.
She's gonna get hurt if we try that.
Why not use your spatial magic to pull her out of there?
Please, be reasonable.
I can't get close to that.
Yeah, okay.
Man, if there were only someone around here who could cancel out magic.
Huh.
You picked the right time to drop in, kid.
Huh?
See that?
Do something about it.
Do something?
Okay, I'll try!
Wait, how am I supposed to get up there?
I can't exactly fly, so...
I don't want to hear your excuses.
Just suck it up, newbie!
Dig deep!
And push past your liver!
I'm dead.
I didn't die!
That was so fun to watch!
More!
I'm all wet now.
Thanks for the portal.
I thought you might appreciate it.
You pulled it off, kid.
Good job.
Thank you!
Hey, Noel!
Noel!
What an abject failure.
Here it comes.
I'm walking.
You know...
You've got yourself some crazy magic power!
I mean, it's freaking amazing!
Really?
I'm totally jealous of you.
I don't have any magic power, like none.
All you need is some training to get it under control.
You'll be strong!
Unstoppable!
Little in...
Asta...
I'm screwed!
Man, I'll have to work extra hard if I'm gonna keep up with you.
What?
Is that all?
You were running away because you can't control your magic power?
Should have said something sooner, you royal failure!
I mean, come on!
This is the Black Bulls, after all.
We're a whole squad of failures.
So maybe you've got a weakness or three.
It doesn't matter to us, you big dummy.
Anyway, we're glad you're all right.
Oh, and I know this place that makes killer pasta.
You want to check it out with me sometime?
Forget about pasta!
So you need to try a bite of this!
Here!
That was quite the show you put on.
I happen to be particularly gifted at controlling my magic power so I can teach you.
Also, maybe give you some womanly advice.
I'll tell you all about what an angel my sister Marie is.
Now come on!
We'll do our best together!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'll tell you all about it.
Thank you.